Guide to the Thelma Z. Lavine papers, 1932-2007
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections & Archives
- Series 2: Research, 1930s-2007; (24.5 boxes)
  - Popular culture and art, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Pragmatism, 1981-2005 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Pragmatism, American, 1990s (Box 22, Folder 10)
    Identified by TZL as "AM new ... Rorty notes."
  - Pragmatism and modernity, 1960s-1980s (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Pragmatism and modernity, 1990s (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Pragmatism, Royce, James, Emerson, undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Pragmatism/Sleeper, 1990s (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Prefaces for 1st and 2nd Ed., Phil 451, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Press coverage and journal reprints, 1980s (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Press, interviews, PR, 1980s (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Professional activities and documentation, 1986-1990 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Progressivism, 1989-1990 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    Identified by TZL as "Progressivism ROM/MOD + END/CONCL"
  - Proudhon, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Psychiatry and the Humanities, forum documents, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Psychohistory, 1981-1983 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Psychology, 1940s-1950s (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Psychology and Durkheim, 1940s (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Publications from TZL, 1950-1977 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - R-W binder contents, 1990s (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Original binder tabs identified contents as "Ricoeur, Russell, Sandel, Schlesinger, Tocqueville, Weber, Whitman, Wittgenstein."
  - Rank seminar, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Rawls and public philosophy, 1979-1982 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Religion and philosophy of history, 1950s-1983 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Religion. Research for Philosophy of History class, 1970s (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Religion and related, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Religion, 1988-1996 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Religion, 1991-1993 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Religious forms, 1940s (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Ricoueur, modernity, Dewey, pragmatism, 1980s (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Ricoeur and Dewey, 1990s (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Robinson lecture, April 9, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Romanticism, undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Romanticism, Smithsonian, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Romanticism, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Rorty, Richard, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Rorty, Richard, 1983-1996 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Rorty, Taylor, Bernstein, 1985-1986 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Rorty, Richard, 1978-1994 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Rosenthal, Sandra, 1990s (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Royalty statement from Bantam Dell, salary from GMU, 1992-1994, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - SAAP, 1974-1990 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - SAAP, 1990s (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - SAAP conference, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - SAAP statement regarding Clinton impeachment proceedings, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Sartre, Jean-Paul, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Schools of thought, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Schutz, Alfred, undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Scientific method lecture at UMD, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Smith College Bulletin, 1937 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Smithsonian papers and Wilson fellowship, 1980s-1990s (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Sociology and history, Salomon, 1960s (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - "SOC-SART AD", undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Social Philosophy, History of Philosophy, various, 1950s-1964 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Social structure, 1995-2001 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Society, 2000s (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Sociology of knowledge, 1942-1951 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Society and knowledge, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - "SOCKN", 1960s-1970s (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Safronsky, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Speeches, talks, review papers, articles, 1961-1974 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Spencer, social Darwinism, 1950s-1972 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Spengler and philosophical history, 1950s (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Structuralism, 1970s-1980s (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Syllabi and supporting notes, 1970s-1980s (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Systems and processes - Warfield research, 1990s (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Teaching notes, Smith College fellowship, 1937-1950s (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Teaching notes, 1940s-1950s (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Teaching notes, 1940s-1950s (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Teaching notes, 1940s-1950s (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Teaching notes, Wells College, 1940s-1960s (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Texas A&M paper, 1980s (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Toynbee, Arnold J., 1940s-1960s (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts, 1 of 2, 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts, 2 of 2, 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Transference, 1980s (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Universality, pragmatism, Diggins, 1971-1996 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Utopia, American issues, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Various, 1950s-1960s (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Various, 1950s-1968 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Various, 1950s-1972 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Various, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Various, 1965-1990 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Includes work on phenomenology, research for Verstehen, Hume, Rorty.
  - Various, 1970s (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Includes notes on American culture and religion, Dewey, ideology.
  - Various, 1 of 2, 1970-1980 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Various, 2 of 2, 1970-1980 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Various, 1976-1989 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Includes notes on various research projects, some newspaper clippings, and a small amount of communication from GWU.
  - Various, 1980s (Box 30, Folder 1)
    Includes notes on American identity, philosophy and culture, women's movement.
  - Various, 1980s-1999 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Various, 1982-1985 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Various, undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Verstehen, philosophy as a vocation, 1951, 1963-1966 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Verstehen, 1954-1988 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Verstehen, 1960s (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Verstehen, 1960s (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Verstehen, 1964, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Vico, Joyce, 1940s-1950s (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Declaration of Rights, 1985-1996 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Foundation for the Humanities, 1989-1992 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - War and morality, 2000s (Box 31, Folder 1)
    Includes research on ethics, religion, philosophy, WWI, Holocaust, Rwanda.
  - Warren Center Fellowship and related research, 1980s (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Washington Philosopher's Club lecture on Cohen by Edel, undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Weber, social sciences, 1950s-1970s (Box 31, Folder 4)
    Includes research for Verstehen and on Abel.
  - Weber symposium, 1960s-1980s (Box 31, Folder 5)
    The Jewish experience, Hegel, Kant. Murphy paper and note.
  - Weber, Max, 1978-1992 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    Includes work on rules, candidates, Feuer.
  - Weber, Max, 1981-1995 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Weber, Max, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Who's Who, undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Wittgenstein, Ludwig, 1963-1978 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Women's movement, 1960s-1980s (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Women's movement, 1970s (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Women's movement, 1970s-1980s (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Women's movement, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Women's movement, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    Preparing for presentation,
  - Women's movement, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Women's movement, undated (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Women's movement, undated (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Women's movement, undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Work process and CVs, 1964-1994 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Zinn, Howard, 1960s-1970 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    Includes work on religion, nihilism, ultimate values as identified by TZL.
- Series 3: Publications, 1977-2002; (2 boxes)
  This series contains original books and professional journals which contain writings from Lavine. A seventh edition English-language copy of her book is present, as well as a copy of the Japanese-language edition. This series is organized chronologically.
  - "Ideas of Revolution in the Women's Movement," by Thelma Z. Lavine in American Behavioral Scientist, March - April, 1977 (Box 32)
    Journal. ABS: American Behavioral Scientist, March/April 1977, Article 6.
  - Introduction by Thelma Z. Lavine for "Transactions of the Charles S. Peirce Society", Spring 1981 (Box 32)
    Journal. Spring, 1981, Vol XVII, No. 2.
  - "Pragmatism and the Constitution in the Culture of Modernism," by Thelma Z. Lavine in "Transactions of the Charles S. Peirce Society", Winter 1984 (Box 32)
    Journal. Transactions of the Charles S. Peirce Society, Winter, 1984, Vol. XX, No. 1,
  - "Judaism in the Culture of Modernism," by Thelma Z. Lavine in "Philosophy, History, and Social Action", 1988 (Box 32)
    Book. Boston Studies in the Philosophy of Science, Vol. 107: Philosophy, History and Social Action: Essays in Honor of Lewis Feuer. Edited by Sidney Hook, William L. O'Neill, Roger O'Toole.
  - "American Pragmatism: Transference and Aufhebung" by Thelma Z. Lavine in "Transactions of the Charles S. Peirce Society", Fall 1988 (Box 32)
    Journal. Transactions of the Charles S. Peirce Society, Fall, 1988, Vol. XXIV, No. 4.
  - Introduction by Thelma Z. Lavine for "John Dewey: Volume 16: 1949-1952", 1989 (Box 32)
    Book. Edited by Jo Ann Boydston.
  - "From Socrates to Sartre," book by Thelma Z. Lavine, 1989 (Box 33)
  - "Postmodernism and American Pragmatism," by Thelma Z. Lavine in "The Journal of Speculative Philosophy", 1993 (Box 33)
    Journal. The Journal of Speculative Philosophy, Vol. VII, No 2.
  - Introduction by Thelma Z. Lavine for "The Process of Government", 1995 (Box 33)
    Book. Author Arthur F. Bentley.
  - "The Process of Government" by Thelma Z. Lavine in "Social Science and Modern Society", January - February 1995 (Box 33)
    Journal. Social Science and Modern Society, Volume 32, No. 2, Jan/Feb 1995.
  - "Reply to Ryan" by Thelma Z. Lavine in "Transactions of the Charles S. Peirce Society", Fall 1997 (Box 33)
    Journal. Transactions of the Charles S. Peirce Society, Fall, 1997, Vol. XXXIII, No. 4.
  - "Philosophy and the Dialectic of Modernity," by Thelma Z. Lavine in "Perspectives on Habermas", 2000 (Box 33)
    Book. Edited by Lewis Edwin Hahn.
  - Introduction by Thelma Z. Lavine for "The Case for Modern Liberalism", 2002 (Box 33)
    Book, used. Author Charles Frankel.
  - Introduction by Thelma Z. Lavine for "The Case for Modern Liberalism", 2002 (Box 33)
    Book, sealed in shrink wrap. Author Charles Frankel.
  - "From Socrates to Sartre," book, by Thelma Z. Lavine, Japanese edition, undated (Box 33)
- Series 4: Audio/Visual, 1969-1996; (10 boxes)
  This series is comprised largely of audiotape cassettes. Included are classroom lectures and radio interviews, as well as a few miscellaneous items such as a memorial speech. Complete or nearly complete lecture series include "From Socrates to Sartre," "Philosophy 19th Century," "Philosophy 355," "Philosophy of America," "Philosophy of History," "Philosophy and Literature/Philosophy of Literature," and "Philosophy and Social Science/Social Philosophy." Items are audiocassettes unless otherwise identified. This series is organized first by medium, then by subject and chronologically.
  - From Socrates to Sartre, lectures 1/2, January 24, 1979, January 30, 1979 (Box 34)
  - From Socrates to Sartre, lectures 3/4, February 5, 1979, February 7, 1979 (Box 34)
  - From Socrates to Sartre, lectures 5/6, February 12, 1979, February 14, 1979 (Box 34)
  - From Socrates to Sartre, lectures 7/8, February 19, 1979, February 21, 1979 (Box 34)
  - From Socrates to Sartre, lectures 9/10, February 26, 1979, February 28, 1979 (Box 34)
  - From Socrates to Sartre, lectures 11/12, March 5, 1979, March 7, 1979 (Box 34)
  - From Socrates to Sartre, lectures 15/16, March 19, 1979, March 21, 1979 (Box 34)
  - From Socrates to Sartre, lectures 17/18, March 31, 1979 (Box 34)
  - From Socrates to Sartre, lectures 19/20, April 2, 1979, April 12, 1982 (Box 34)
  - From Socrates to Sartre, lectures 25/26, April 28, 1979 (Box 34)
  - From Socrates to Sartre, lectures 27/28, April 30, 1979, May 2, 1979 (Box 34)
  - From Socrates to Sartre, lectures 29/30, May 7, 1979, May 9, 1979 (Box 34)
  - From Socrates to Sartre, lectures 13/14, March 22, 1980 (Box 34)
  - From Socrates to Sartre, lectures 21/22, April 19, 1980 (Box 34)
  - From Socrates to Sartre, lectures 23/24, April 21, 1980, April 28, 1980 (Box 34)
  - Philosophy 19th Century, October 3, 1983 (Box 34)
  - Philosophy 19th Century, October 5, 1983 (Box 34)
  - Philosophy 19th Century, October 10, 1983 (Box 34)
  - Philosophy 19th Century, October 12, 1983 (Box 34)
  - Philosophy 19th Century, October 17, 1983 (Box 34)
  - Philosophy 19th Century, October 19, 1983 (Box 34)
  - Philosophy 19th Century, October 24, 1983 (Box 34)
  - Philosophy 19th Century, October 26, 1983 (Box 34)
  - Philosophy 19th Century, October 31, 1983 (Box 34)
  - Philosophy 19th Century, November 2, 1983 (Box 34)
  - Philosophy 19th Century, November 7, 1983 (Box 34)
  - Philosophy 19th Century, November 9, 1983 (Box 34)
  - Philosophy 19th Century, November 14, 1983 (Box 34)
  - Philosophy 19th Century, November 16, 1983 (Box 34)
  - Philosophy 19th Century, November 21, 1983 (Box 34)
  - Philosophy 19th Century, November 23, 1983 (Box 34)
  - Philosophy 19th Century, November 28, 1983 (Box 34)
  - Philosophy 19th Century, November 30, 1983 (Box 34)
  - Philosophy 19th Century, December 5, 1983 (Box 34)
  - Philosophy 19th Century, "END", December 7, 1983 (Box 35)
  - Philosophy 355, No. 1, undated (Box 35)
  - Philosophy 355, No. 2, undated (Box 35)
  - Philosophy 355, No. 3, undated (Box 35)
  - Philosophy 355, No. 4, undated (Box 35)
  - Philosophy 355, No. 5, undated (Box 35)
  - Philosophy 355, No. 6, undated (Box 35)
  - Philosophy 355, No. 7, undated (Box 35)
  - Philosophy 355, No. 8, undated (Box 35)
  - Philosophy 355, No. 9, undated (Box 35)
  - Philosophy 355, No. 10, undated (Box 35)
  - Philosophy 355, No. 11, undated (Box 35)
  - Philosophy 355, No. 12, undated (Box 35)
  - Philosophy 355, No. 13, undated (Box 35)
  - Philosophy 355, No. 14, undated (Box 35)
  - Philosophy 355, No. 15, undated (Box 35)
  - Philosophy 355, No. 16, undated (Box 35)
  - Philosophy 355, No. 17, undated (Box 35)
  - Philosophy 355, No. 18, undated (Box 35)
  - Philosophy 355, No. 19, undated (Box 35)
  - Philosophy 355, No. 20, undated (Box 35)
  - Philosophy 355, No. 21, undated (Box 35)
  - Philosophy 355, No. 22, undated (Box 35)
  - Philosophy 355, No. 23, undated (Box 35)
  - Philosophy 355, No. 24, undated (Box 35)
  - Philosophy 355, No. 25, undated (Box 35)
  - Philosophy 355, No. 26, undated (Box 35)
  - Philosophy of America, 1, September 4, 1991 (Box 35)
  - Philosophy of America, 2, September 5, 1991 (Box 35)
  - Philosophy of America, 3, September 10, 1991 (Box 35)
  - Philosophy of America, 4, September 12, 1991 (Box 35)
  - Philosophy of America, 5, September 17, 1991 (Box 35)
  - Philosophy of America, 6, September 19, 1991 (Box 35)
  - Philosophy of America, 7, September 24, 1991 (Box 35)
  - Philosophy of America, 8, September 26, 1991 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of America, 9, October 1, 1991 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of America, 10, October 3, 1991 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of America, 12, October 10, 1991 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of America, 13, October 16, 1991 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of America, 14, October 22, 1991 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of America, 16, November 5, 1991 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of America, 17, November 7, 1991 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of America, 18, November 12, 1991 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of America, 19, November 14, 1991 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of America, 20, November 19, 1991 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of America, 21, November 21, 1991 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of America, 22, November 26, 1991 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of America, 23, December 3, 1991 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of America, 24, December 5, 1991 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of America, 25, December 10, 1991 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of America, 26, December 12, 1991 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of History, October 3, 1983 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of History, October 5, 1983 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of History, October 10, 1983 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of History, October 12, 1983 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of History, October 17, 1983 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of History, October 19, 1983 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of History, October 24, 1983 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of History, October 26, 1983 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of History, October 31, 1983 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of History, November 2, 1983 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of History, November 7, 1983 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of History, November 9, 1983 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of History, November 14, 1983 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of History, November 16, 1983 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of History, November 21, 1983 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of History, November 23, 1983 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of History, November 28, 1983 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy of History, November 30, 1983 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy of History, December 5, 1983 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy & Literature, January 16, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy & Literature, Sophocles, January 23, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy & Literature, Sophocles, January 26, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy & Literature, Sophocles, January 30, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy & Literature, Sophocles, February 1, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy & Literature, Freud, February 6, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy & Literature, Freud, February 8, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy & Literature, Freud, February 13, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy & Literature, Freud, February 22, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy & Literature, DM Thomas, February 22, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy & Literature, T. Mann: Tonio Kroeger, February 29, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy & Literature, T. Mann, March 5, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy & Literature, Mann, March 7, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy & Literature, Mann. Z.B., March 19, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy & Literature, Mann, March 21, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy & Literature, Mann, March 26, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy & Literature, Hesse, April 2, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy & Literature, Hesse, April 4, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy & Literature, Hesse, April 9, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy & Literature, Kafka, April 11, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy & Literature, Freud on Women, April 15, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy & Literature, Kafka, April 16, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy & Literature, Kafka/Existentialism, April 18, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy & Literature, Camus, April 23, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy of Literature, 1, September 3, 1991 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy of Literature, 2, September 5, 1991 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy of Literature, 3, September 10, 1991 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy of Literature, 4, September 12, 1991 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy of Literature, 5, September 17, 1991 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy of Literature, 6, September 19, 1991 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy of Literature, 7, September 24, 1991 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy of Literature, 9, October 1, 1991 (Box 37)
  - Philosophy of Literature, 10, October 3, 1991 (Box 38)
  - Philosophy of Literature, 12, October 10, 1991 (Box 38)
  - Philosophy of Literature, 13, October 17, 1991 (Box 38)
  - Philosophy of Literature, 14, October 22, 1991 (Box 38)
  - Philosophy of Literature, 15, October 24, 1991 (Box 38)
  - Philosophy of Literature, 16, November 5, 1991 (Box 38)
  - Philosophy of Literature, 17, November 7, 1991 (Box 38)
  - Philosophy of Literature, 18, November 12, 1991 (Box 38)
  - Philosophy of Literature, 19, November 21, 1991 (Box 38)
  - Philosophy of Literature, 20, November 21, 1991 (Box 38)
  - Philosophy of Literature, 21, November 26, 1991 (Box 38)
  - Philosophy of Literature, 23, December 5, 1991 (Box 38)
  - Philosophy of Literature, 24, December 10, 1991 (Box 38)
  - Philosophy of Literature, 25, December 12, 1991 (Box 38)
  - Philosophy and Literature, No. 1, undated (Box 38)
  - Philosophy and Literature, No. 2, undated (Box 38)
  - Philosophy and Literature, No. 3, undated (Box 38)
  - Philosophy and Literature, No. 4, undated (Box 38)
  - Philosophy and Literature, No. 5, undated (Box 38)
  - Philosophy and Literature, No. 6, undated (Box 38)
  - Philosophy and Literature, No. 7, undated (Box 38)
  - Philosophy and Literature, No. 8, undated (Box 38)
  - Philosophy and Literature, No. 9, undated (Box 38)
  - Philosophy and Literature, No. 10, undated (Box 38)
  - Philosophy and Literature, No. 11, undated (Box 38)
  - Philosophy and Literature, No. 12, undated (Box 38)
  - Philosophy and Literature, No. 13, undated (Box 38)
  - Philosophy and Literature, No. 14, undated (Box 38)
  - Philosophy and Literature, No. 15, undated (Box 38)
  - Philosophy and Literature, No. 16, undated (Box 38)
  - Philosophy and Literature, No. 17, undated (Box 38)
  - Philosophy and Literature, No. 18, undated (Box 38)
  - Philosophy and Literature, No. 19, undated (Box 38)
  - Philosophy and Literature, No. 20, undated (Box 38)
  - Philosophy and Literature, No. 21, undated (Box 39)
  - Philosophy and Literature, No. 22, undated (Box 39)
  - Philosophy and Literature, No. 23, undated (Box 39)
  - Philosophy and Literature, No. 24, undated (Box 39)
  - Philosophy and Literature, No. 25, undated (Box 39)
  - Philosophy and Literature, No. 26, undated (Box 39)
  - Philosophy and Social Science, October 3, 1983 (Box 39)
  - Philosophy and Social Science, October 10, 1983 (Box 39)
  - Philosophy and Social Science, October 17, 1983 (Box 39)
  - Philosophy and Social Science, October 24, 1983 (Box 39)
  - Philosophy and Social Science, October 31, 1983 (Box 39)
  - Philosophy and Social Science, November 7, 1983 (Box 39)
  - Philosophy and Social Science, November 14, 1983 (Box 39)
  - Philosophy and Social Science, November 21, 1983 (Box 39)
  - Philosophy and Social Science, November 28, 1983 (Box 39)
  - Philosophy and Social Science, December 5, 1983 (Box 39)
  - Philosophy of Social Science, September 6, 1984 (Box 39)
  - Philosophy of Social Science, September 13, 1984 (Box 39)
  - Philosophy of Social Science, September 20, 1984 (Box 39)
  - Philosophy of Social Science, September 27, 1984 (Box 39)
  - Social Philosophy Intro, January 16, 1984 (Box 39)
  - Social Philosophy, January 23, 1984 (Box 39)
  - Social Philosophy, January 25, 1984 (Box 39)
  - Social Philosophy, January 30, 1984 (Box 39)
  - Social Philosophy, February 1, 1984 (Box 39)
  - Social Philosophy, February 6, 1984 (Box 39)
  - Social Philosophy, Locke, February 8, 1984 (Box 39)
  - Social Philosophy, Locke, February 13, 1984 (Box 39)
  - Social Philosophy, Locke, February 15, 1984 (Box 39)
  - Social Philosophy, February 22, 1984 (Box 39)
  - Social Philosophy, February 27, 1984 (Box 39)
  - Social Philosophy, Rousseau, February 29, 1984 (Box 39)
  - Social Philosophy, Rousseau, March 5, 1984 (Box 39)
  - Social Philosophy, Rousseau, March 7, 1984 (Box 39)
  - Social Philosophy, March 19, 1984 (Box 40)
  - Social Philosophy, Godwin, March 21, 1984 (Box 40)
  - Social Philosophy, Godwin, March 26, 1984 (Box 40)
  - Social Philosophy, Godwin, March 28, 1984 (Box 40)
  - Social Philosophy, Proudhom, April 2, 1984 (Box 40)
  - Social Philosophy, Proudhom, April 4, 1984 (Box 40)
  - Social Philosophy, Proudhom, April 9, 1984 (Box 40)
  - Social Philosophy, Marx, April 11, 1984 (Box 40)
  - Social Philosophy, Marx, April 16, 1984 (Box 40)
  - Social Philosophy, Marx, April 18, 1984 (Box 40)
  - Social Philosophy, Marx, April 22, 1984 (Box 40)
  - Various, Goldkey, 1969-1970 (Box 40)
  - Various, Dewey-Sartre Paper, December 16, 1976 (Box 40)
    Fordham Univ.
  - Various, Otto Rank Seminar, October 11, 1979 (Box 40)
    Philosophical Roots - German - Freud - Rank
  - Various, LDS, 12 - 1 am, January 19, 1980 (Box 40)
  - Various, LDS, 1 - 2 am, January 19, 1980 (Box 40)
  - Various, LDS, 2 - 3 am, January 19, 1980 (Box 40)
  - Various, German Philosophy and Judaism, March 16, 1980 (Box 40)
    Wash. Hebrew Congregation, Scholar Series
  - Various, W.O.A. Thelma Lavine, February 10, 1982 (Box 40)